giftcardrescue.com 2015-09-05

# Our Privacy Policy : Buy Gift Cards Online : Gift Cards | GiftCardRescue

Thank you for choosing Giftcardrescue.com. We would like you to know that your privacy is extremely important to us. Therefore we ensure that information, gathered and stored in our database will be kept confidential and will not be shared with any outside sources, without your knowledge and given permission.

By visiting Giftcardrescue.com, you acknowledge that you have read and agree to follow the Privacy Policy described below. If you do not agree to the terms of our privacy policy discussed here, you should exit this website now, and you should not review information or obtain items from this website.

## What Personal Customer Information Does Giftcardrescue.com Collect?

Our primary goal in collecting personal information is to provide Giftcardrescue.com’s visitors with superior online experience. We use the customer contact information to fill orders, contact purchasers to inform them of their order status, to send promotional information, to enhance the operation of our site and administer our systems.

We gather information in the following ways:

## Registration

In order to process your orders placed on this website, you must first complete the registration form. During registration, you will be required to provide your contact information, which includes your name, e-mail address, telephone number and street address. This information is used to provide you with important Giftcardrescue.com services such as automated order status updates via e-mail.

## Order

Most of the information collected in the registration process will be used to process orders. During the order process, you may be directed to third party payment processing sites such as PayPal or Authorize.net to make payment for your order or receive payment for a gift card sold to Giftcardrescue.com.

## Cookies

Our site uses cookies to store information. Cookies are small pieces of information that are stored by your browser on your computer’s hard drive. We use cookies to remember your name and your customer ID number. This allows you to leave our site, come back later, and still view contents in your Wish List and/or purchases made in the past. These cookies allow us to better understand, in aggregate, the preferences of our users and thereby create new services that better attend to those preferences. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually change your browser to prevent that. Even without a cookie, you can still use most of the features in our store, including placing items in your shopping cart and purchasing them.

**Does Giftcardrescue.com Share the Information It Receives?**

We may disclose personal information to respond to legal requirements, enforce our policies, or protect anyone’s rights, property, or safety.

We may also share your personal information with:

  1. Affiliated Businesses: We may share any information that you supply to us with any affiliated business that is substantially controlled by Giftcardrescue.com, LLC. Any information that is shared this way will be subject to this Privacy Policy.
  2. Vendors: We provide some of our vendors with your contact information so that they may contact you directly with product support information.
  3. Payment processing companies and shippers: When you buy something from us, we send your information to third party payment processing companies (PayPal or Authorize.net) to facilitate the payment process. Giftcardrescue.com only accepts credit card payments (which are processed through Authorize.net)and only makes payment for gift cards we purchase through PayPal. Your name, telephone number and shipping information may be provided to third party shippers such as UPS, Federal Express and the United States Postal Service to deliver your purchase.
  4. Third Party Ads, Surveys and Promotions: We may use third parties to display ads, surveys and various promotions on our site. These will always be labeled with the third party name. These third party applications may contain cookies or other code which are outside of our control. Although we will attempt to only work with third parties who respect your privacy, we are not responsible or liable for any information collected by these third parties or how it is used. You should contact the third party directly or check the third party’s Privacy Policy to see how any information that they may gather will be used.
  5. Link to Third Party Site: Our Web site contains links to third party sites, such as our vendors. Giftcardrescue.com is not responsible or liable for the privacy practices or content found on these sites. We suggest that you check the Privacy Privacy of each site you visit.
  6. Third Party Checkout Links: If you use a third party checkout link on our site such as Google Checkout or PayPal, your name, billing and shipping addresses is transferred to us from your account with the third party to enable you to check out of our site without having to re-enter certain information.
  7. Independent Contractors: We may employ other companies or individuals to provide certain services to us such as sending e-mail, providing click to call telephone calling services, analyzing customer lists and data, providing marketing assistance, or consulting services. These third parties will have access to the information needed to perform their functions but cannot use that information for any other purpose.
  8. Other third parties to whom you explicitly ask us to send your information (or about whom you are otherwise explicitly notified and consent to when using a specific service).
  9. Law enforcement or other governmental officials, in response to a verified request relating to a criminal investigation or alleged illegal activity. In such events, we will disclose information relevant to the investigation, such as name, city, state, zip code, telephone number, email address, User ID history, IP address, and fraud complaints.

## Testimonials

The testimonials section of the Giftcardrescue.com website is for the purpose of sharing positive experiences that you had with Giftcardrescue.com. The testimonials section is moderated to ensure accurate and positive testimonials. Published testimonials are genuine, but Giftcardrescue.com reserves the right to edit or alter such to remove personal information, statements that may be a violation of law, or statements that may infringe on the rights of Giftcardrescue.com or third parties. Giftcardrescue.com reserves the right to post or remove any testimonial at its discretion.

By posting your comment(s) or testimonial(s) (“Testimonial”) on our website, you give us permission to reprint or use the Testimonial in connection with our businesses (including but not limited to the marketing and selling of various products and services, as well as the marketing of Giftcardrescue.com). You also are agreeing to the following: (1) The reprint or use of the Testimonial will be at our discretion and without compensation to you; (2) We may use the Testimonial with or without any pseudo (pen) name credit; (3) Our right to use the Testimonial is perpetual and may be assigned by us; (4) We may use the Testimonial locally, nationally or globally and such use may be made in any media, information or communication platform (including Internet advertising) currently in use or later developed; (5) You and not someone else composed and posted the Testimonial; (6) Giftcardrescue.com may allow any of its parents, subsidiaries or affiliates to use the Testimonial in the same manner as set forth herein but in relation to their businesses and websites; and (7) We may edit or alter such Testimonial to remove personal information, statements that may be a violation of law, or statements that may infringe on the rights of Giftcardrescue.com or third parties.

Other than your pseudo (pen) name, which we may or may not use, your personal contact information will not be disclosed in connection with our reprint or use of your Testimonial.

## Email This Page

If you choose to use our referral service to tell a friend about our site, we will ask you for your friend’s name and email address. We will automatically send your friend a one-time email inviting him or her to visit the site. Giftcardrescue.com does not store this information and only uses this information for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email.

## Children

If you make a purchase, sale or exchange on Giftcardrescue.com, you are representing that you are an adult. If you are a child under the age of 13, you must ask your parent or guardian to assist you in using Giftcardrescue.com.

## Choice/Opt-Out

Our Web site gives you the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us. If you no longer wish to receive communications from us, you may contact us at customerservice@giftcardrescue.com.

## Your consent to this policy

By using the Giftcardrescue.com web site, you agree to this Privacy Policy. This is our entire and exclusive Privacy Policy and it supersedes any earlier version. Our Terms and Conditions take precedence over any conflicting Policy provision. We may change our Privacy Policy by posting a new version of the policy on this page which it is your responsibility to review frequently.

## Legal disclaimer

This Site operates AS-IS and AS-AVAILABLE, without liability of any kind. We are not responsible for events beyond our direct control. This Privacy Policy is governed by Maryland law, excluding conflicts of law principles. Any legal action against us is exclusively subject to the jurisdiction of the courts of the state of Maryland.

If you have a privacy question about the Giftcardrescue.com web site, please click here to contact us. Or write to:

GC Rescue Attention: Customer Service 6230 Old Dobbin Lane, Suite 190 Columbia, MD 21045

__Updated on February 5, 2009
